{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Waste \u0026 Junk Removal Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40375/":{"taskOID":40375,"originalTaskOID":40375,"setID":669,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4266,"questionDisplayText":"What Needs to be Hauled","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What do you have that needs to be hauled away? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":873,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Assorted junk from inside garage or house","answerDisplayText":"Assorted junk from inside garage or house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1595,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Construction debris such as wood, drywall, concrete, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Construction debris such as wood, drywall, concrete, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7142,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Yard clippings","answerDisplayText":"Yard clippings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3713,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Major appliance, bulky furniture, mattress, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Major appliance, bulky furniture, mattress, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6383,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tires","answerDisplayText":"Tires","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1577,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Concrete removed from patio, walk, driveway, wall, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Concrete removed from patio, walk, driveway, wall, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4265,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Hauling","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the work to be done in conjunction with the hauling?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":4396,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One-time yard clean-up","answerDisplayText":"One-time yard clean-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4958,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pruning and trimming landscape","answerDisplayText":"Pruning and trimming landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1920,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Digging","answerDisplayText":"Digging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1871,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Demolition of shed, swing set, etc. (requiring use of tools)","answerDisplayText":"Demolition of shed, swing set, etc. (requiring use of tools)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3990,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Moving items around and out of house, basement, or garage","answerDisplayText":"Moving items around and out of house, basement, or garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1870,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Demolition and removal of concrete","answerDisplayText":"Demolition and removal of concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4266,"questionDisplayText":"What Needs to be Hauled","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What do you have that needs to be hauled away? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":873,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Assorted junk from inside garage or house","answerDisplayText":"Assorted junk from inside garage or house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1595,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Construction debris such as wood, drywall, concrete, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Construction debris such as wood, drywall, concrete, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7142,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Yard clippings","answerDisplayText":"Yard clippings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3713,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Major appliance, bulky furniture, mattress, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Major appliance, bulky furniture, mattress, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6383,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tires","answerDisplayText":"Tires","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1577,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Concrete removed from patio, walk, driveway, wall, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Concrete removed from patio, walk, driveway, wall, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":873,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Assorted junk from inside garage or house","answerDisplayText":"Assorted junk from inside garage or house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1595,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Construction debris such as wood, drywall, concrete, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Construction debris such as wood, drywall, concrete, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7142,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Yard clippings","answerDisplayText":"Yard clippings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3713,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Major appliance, bulky furniture, mattress, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Major appliance, bulky furniture, mattress, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6383,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tires","answerDisplayText":"Tires","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1577,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Concrete removed from patio, walk, driveway, wall, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Concrete removed from patio, walk, driveway, wall, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4265,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Hauling","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the work to be done in conjunction with the hauling?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":4396,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One-time yard clean-up","answerDisplayText":"One-time yard clean-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4958,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pruning and trimming landscape","answerDisplayText":"Pruning and trimming landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1920,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Digging","answerDisplayText":"Digging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1871,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Demolition of shed, swing set, etc. (requiring use of tools)","answerDisplayText":"Demolition of shed, swing set, etc. (requiring use of tools)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3990,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Moving items around and out of house, basement, or garage","answerDisplayText":"Moving items around and out of house, basement, or garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1870,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Demolition and removal of concrete","answerDisplayText":"Demolition and removal of concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4396,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One-time yard clean-up","answerDisplayText":"One-time yard clean-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4958,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pruning and trimming landscape","answerDisplayText":"Pruning and trimming landscape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1920,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Digging","answerDisplayText":"Digging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1871,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Demolition of shed, swing set, etc. (requiring use of tools)","answerDisplayText":"Demolition of shed, swing set, etc. (requiring use of tools)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3990,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Moving items around and out of house, basement, or garage","answerDisplayText":"Moving items around and out of house, basement, or garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1870,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Demolition and removal of concrete","answerDisplayText":"Demolition and removal of concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40375/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40375,"taskName":"Waste, Junk, Building Materials and Debris - Remove and Haul","taskDescription":"Haul Waste, Junk, Debris and Building Materials to the Dump","xmTaskDescriptor":"Waste \u0026 Junk Removal Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":261,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Building rock property Waste Dump","textMessagingName":"Trash Removal","rolloverLongDesc":"Get rid of appliances, building materials, trash, junk, landscape debris, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Get rid of appliances, building materials, trash, junk, landscape debris, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Haul Waste, Junk, Debris and Building Materials to the Dump.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Waste \u0026 Junk Removal \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Trash \u0026 Garbage Removal Companies","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":81,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Remove \u0026 Haul Waste, Junk, Debris, etc.","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Waste, Junk, Building Materials and Debris - Remove and Haul","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Waste \u0026 Junk Removal Project","urlName":"Waste-Junk-Building-Materials-and-Debris-Remove-and-Haul","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Junk \u0026 Waste Removal Services \u003cin_city\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Building,rock,property,Waste,Dump,Junk,Haul,Removal,trash,site,Clean,UP,construction,job,debris,Materials","emcCategoryOid":-12076,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":669,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}